Mauro Ezequiel Bender

Curriculum Vitae

Dragones 2717, Gonzalez Catan 1759 Buenos Aires, Argentina $\mathfrak{D} + 54$ 11 3911 4033 $\mathfrak{T} + 54$ 11 2005 0307 $\mathfrak{D} = 54$ maurobender@gmail.com



"Success is the ability to go from failure to failure without losing your enthusiasm." – Winston Churchill

Info

Born January 16th, 1988 at Buenos Aires Citizenship Argentine

(Argentina)

LinkedIn http://ar.linkedin.com/in/ Skype mauro.bender

maurobender

Desidered Employment and Current Skills

System Administrator, DBA, Programmer, Consultant

Over the years, thanks to my thirst for knowledge, I have gained extensive experience in computer science ranging from operating systems to programming languages and platforms upon which the latter are based. Along this path I have continued to improve my approach to problems always trying to implement optimal, generalized and reusable solutions (OOP, Design Patterns). In some academic work opportunities I've been able to demonstrate excellent teamwork skills and capability to collaborate with external groups. Another virtue I possess is the ability to solve almost any computer problem thanks to the excellent information gathering skills and the many years of experience in the computer science field.

Computer Skills

Languages JAVA, JavaScript, C, C++, SQL, PHP, HTML5, CSS3, LESS, PYTHON, BASH, LATEX, Doxygen, Qt. Gtk

Platforms Unix, Linux, Windows, Apache, Node.js DB MySQL, PostgrSQL

Tools Eclipse IDE, Netbeans IDE, CMAKE Build system, ANT Build system, Git, SVN, AJAX, jQuery, JSON, Office Suite, Photoshop, Gimp

Experience

Working

2009-Now **Web Developer**, *Insite*, Buenos Aires, Argentina.

Windows Server2008/2010 and MSSQL Server 2008/2010 administration, creation and modification of T-SQL stored procedures and SQL queries, development of ASP.NET/C# based websites, development of C# applications and general computer consultancy.

Other

2011-2012 Web Developer & Co-Founder, Vitbok.

Vitbok is a social network based in the idea of recreate a person's personal diary. In Vitbok you can share you "day a day" an then, afterwards, return and remember what you did that day. You can also post pictures and postits in your diary's page, dragging them to wherever you want. The postits are also helpful as reminders of future appointments. You're diary can be, both, private (it can be seen by only you) or shared (your friends can also see it).

Education

2006- Licentiate in Computer Science, Universidad de Buenos Aires, Buenos Aires, Argentina.

2002-2005 **Electronic Technician high school Diploma**, *E.E.T N*^o *6*, Buenos Aires, Argentina. Course of studies in Electronics.

Languages

Spanish Mother Tongue

English Intermediate

French Basic

Interests and Hobbies

I love any sport but I prefer Basketball and Ping Pong. I enjoy reading technical and classic literature books but I don't mind psychology and novels either. I love fishing and diving even if I don't practice really often that activities unfortunately.

Extra

QOO Simple PHP framework written with MVC (OOP) programming in mind that I worked on with a friend of mine.

- o GitHub Repository
- Qoo Framework Blog